# SAVANA ALDEN

## FRONTEND TECH LEAD

## CONTACT

savana@youaremysunshine.design youaremysunshine.design 587.578.1069

### **SKILLS**

## **Technical**

HTML/CSS
Javascript
Handlebars
React & Vue
Github
SVN
Craft CMS

#### Not So Technical

Sketch
Adobe XD
Photoshop
Illustrator
After Effects

### **EDUCATION**

## North Idaho College

Web Design AAS SEP 2013 - DEC 2016

## **ABOUT**

Savana is a frontend web developer with an eye for design. She is also passionate about animation and creating a user friendly and accessible web experience. She is a project lead and enjoys finding creative solutions to technical problems. In her spare time she enjoys drawing, travelling, reading, and talking in the third person.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### **Critical Mass**

Tech Lead	Senior Developer	Developer
2023 - PRESENT	2022 - 2023	2020 - 2022

Client: Apple

Created a dynamic and organized system to execute projects more efficiently. Leads projects and oversees the deployment. Works on multiple teams with using various tech stacks. Supervises other developers on projects. Solo and team projects. Works on multiple campaigns simultaneously. Works on tight deadlines with proficiency. Executes prototypes of designers' visions using only HTML & CSS.

#### 14Four

## Frontend Developer

SEP 2018 - AUG 2020

Partial client list: Svedka Vodka, Quaker Oats, Adidas, Ruffles, Constellation Brands, Mountain Dew, AT&T

Worked with Craft CMS to create websites so clients can maintain the content while the frontend stays unique in it's design and functionality. Created single page applications with React and Vue. Worked with a team on multiple different canvas based web games integrating React or Vue with my responsibilities involving the UI.